<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Keith Dunstan</title>
    <link>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Keith Dunstan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/a_nice_suburb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/a_nice_suburb/</guid>
      <description>A Nice Suburb It is much easier to write a novel or an autobiography if you have been miserable as a child, persecuted, tortured or banished. That is why the Russians Dostoevsky, Tolstoy, Turgenev and Gogol remain the greatest writers. Not only were they able to draw on their own emotional, anguished lives; they were also able to call upon the sufferings of their country: upon the poverty, the class conflicts, the frigid winters, the wars and the subjugation of the Russian people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/education_by_flagelation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/education_by_flagelation/</guid>
      <description>Education by flagellation So many people look upon school-days as the happiest time of their life. For me school was little pleasure. I suspect my misery was self-inflicted. Home was such a warm, pleasurable place; school such a hideous, disciplined contrast. At the age of 7 1 was dispatched to Wadhurst, the preparatory school for Melbourne Grammar, which was in the grounds of the senior school. Melbourne Grammar, Anglican, bluestone, was created by Bishop Perry in 1849 and was one of the great public schools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/index_of_contents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/index_of_contents/</guid>
      <description>Index of contents St Catherine&amp;rsquo;s school 12 Ste Anne&amp;rsquo;s 6-8, 11, 28, 40, 80,164,186 Saturday matinees 35 Scherger, Air Commodore F. R. W. 83, 103, 104, 106 Schofield, Margaret 133 school athletics 53-4 school cadets 82-3 Schultze, Albert 237, 240 Schultze, Wilma 237 Scotch College 23, 24 Scotts Hotel 170 Scrooge Society 206 sea travel 141-2 Second World War 64, 65-6, 70, 71-2,74-8 see also Royal Australian Air Force Sharpley, Cecil Herbert 187-9 Sherman, Stan 151 shipping round 114 Siple, Greg 230 Sister C.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Doing this is like sitting naked in the bath while a television crew films you for the &amp;lsquo;Today&amp;rsquo; show. A dreadful experience. So why do it? Vanity? It is an act of vanity, yes. But I must put in a plea of guilty with extenuating circumstances.
Heaven knows how many times I have thought about my great-grandfather John Dunstan, a tin miner who was born in Penryn, Cornwall, in 1833.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/siberia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/siberia/</guid>
      <description>Siberia The Geelong Road in 1939 was the epitome of dreariness. One proceeded out past Flemington race-track, through Footscray, through industrial Deer Park, then on to a treeless, rocky plain. The plain seemed waterless, burnt, grey. The only feature, over there to the right, was those humps, rather mysterious, all alone - the You Yangs. The road passed through Werribee, a small town, but I always had a feeling of passing through a wasteland.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>