<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Manual on Grand Central Apartments</title>
    <link>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Manual on Grand Central Apartments</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1. Introduction</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/introduction/</guid>
      <description>1.1.	Purpose and scope The purpose of this Owners and Residents Manual is to provide information to assist Lot Owners and tenants to live harmoniously and safely at Grand Central Apartments.
The scope of the Manual includes useful contact information for tradespeople who have knowledge and experience at Grand Central Apartments, moving in, around and out of the building, security, recreational facilities, procedures adopted by the Owners Corporation relevant to Lot Owners (such as renovation procedures), and the Owners Corporation Rules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. Principal service providers</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/principal-service-providers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/principal-service-providers/</guid>
      <description>2.1.	Owners Corporation manager Civium Property Group ensures that administrative, financial and regulatory requirements are managed in a timely and effective manner. These include:
 Communication with Lot Owners and Agents, such as the distribution of agenda and meeting minutes, administering ballots, and general correspondence. Invoicing levy amounts, collecting any overdue fees and account enquiries. Paying bills on behalf of the Owners Corporation. Maintaining bank and other financial accounts. Regulatory requirements, such as appropriate insurance coverage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3. Contact list</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/contact-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/contact-list/</guid>
      <description>Table 2 lists useful contacts for Lot Owners and residents. Some matters are the responsibility of individual Lot Owners (such as internet access), however some companies are listed that have experience in Grand Central Apartments. To that extent, they may provide knowledgeable service. The Owners Corporation does not endorse and is not responsible for the performance of service providers engaged by Lot Owners.
Table 2 – Service providers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4. Moving in and out</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/moving-in-and-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/moving-in-and-out/</guid>
      <description>Where moving in and out of the Grand Central includes moving furniture and other bulky items, the move must be coordinated with the Building Manager. A loading bay is available near the southern entrance to the rear car park, where moving vans and trucks may be unloaded and loaded.
When moving in for the first time, the Building Manager will provide new residents with induction training, including where to place rubbish, how to access the building and common areas (such as the barbecues and swimming pool), and where to get mail, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5. Building access</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/building-access/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/building-access/</guid>
      <description>5.1.	Security A security system is installed to prevent unauthorised access to the building, rear courtyard and car park. The effective operation of security elements of the building is the collective responsibility of all residents and visitors (including tradespeople).
Electronic locks restrict access to the following areas.
 In and out of the building (and to Levels 1, 2 and 3). To the rear courtyard and barbecues. To the swimming pool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6. Apartment services</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/apartment-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/apartment-services/</guid>
      <description>6.1.	Concierge Grand Central Apartments does not have a concierge service. The principal service providers only work during normal business hours. Residents should not use the Hotel as a proxy for a concierge. Whilst the Hotel and residents live and work together, the Hotel is a business and should not be treated as an after-hours service provider to greet resident’s guests, receive packages or food deliveries, or solve apartment after-hours service problems (such as electricity failure or dripping taps).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7. Waste</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/waste/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/waste/</guid>
      <description>7.1.	General and recycling Except for Level 1, there are two rubbish rooms, located at the northern and southern end of each level. The rubbish rooms include separate bins for recycling. Residents should sort domestic rubbish, mixed recycling waste and cardboard waste, and place it in the appropriate bins.
7.2.	Hard waste Hard waste (large items, such as appliances) is generally collected every three months. The Building Manager will notify residents when a collection is imminent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8. Maintenance</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/maintenance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/maintenance/</guid>
      <description>8.1.	Plumbing and drainage Plumbing and drainage within an apartment is the responsibility of the Lot Owner. This includes leaking taps, burst hot water services and blocked drains.
Where water is entering an apartment from an adjacent apartment, then the Owners Corporation may investigate the cause of the leak and have the leak stopped to prevent damage. Such leaks will be investigated to determine the cause. Where a leak is caused by a failure of common property, then the Owners Corporation will pay for the costs of rectification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9. Parking </title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/parking/</guid>
      <description>9.1.	General Parking is only available in designated car park lots in the car park building at the rear of the main building. Limited parking is available in the loading bay while loading and unloading furniture and other bulky items. The common area at the south of the building (around the fountain) is not a recognised car park.
9.2.	Car park building Vehicles can only be parked in designated park lots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10. Recreation</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/recreation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/recreation/</guid>
      <description>10.1.	Swimming pool The swimming pool on Level 1 is open each day from 0600 to 2200. General safety and social responsibility rules apply in and around the swimming pool.
10.2.	Spa The spa is adjacent to the swimming pool. The spa is open each day from 0600 to 2200. Foreign products (such as soap) should not be added to the spa.
10.3.	Sauna The sauna is owned by the Hotel and with its consent, may be used by all residents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11. Renovations</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/renovations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/renovations/</guid>
      <description>Renovations within an apartment may be lengthy and disruptive to other residents. Lot Owners need to be aware that Heritage Victoria restrictions apply to the whole of the building and surrounding land. Changes may affect heritage aspects of the building and need to be approved. Annex 5 provides details of a procedure adopted to regulate renovations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12. Special Rules</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/special-rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/special-rules/</guid>
      <description>The Special Rules in Annex 6 are adopted by the Owners Corporation to control, manage and administer the use and enjoyment of common property.
Lot Owners and residents (including tenants) should be familiar with the Special Rules. The Special Rules include both positive and negative obligations on all Owners, residents and their guests. A breach of the Special Rules may result in action taken by the Owners Corporation to remedy the breach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annex 1 – Move in, Move out, Induction</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/annex-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/annex-1/</guid>
      <description>This page is in draft</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annex 2 – Access Tokens and Apartment Door Keys</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/annex-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/annex-2/</guid>
      <description>This page is in draft</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annex 3 – Use of Car Park by Non-Residents</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/annex-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/annex-3/</guid>
      <description>This page is in draft</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annex 4 – Car Park Storage Pods and Bollards</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/annex-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/annex-4/</guid>
      <description>This page is in draft</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annex 5 – Renovations</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/annex-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/annex-5/</guid>
      <description>This page is in draft</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annex 6 – Special Rules</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/annex-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/annex-6/</guid>
      <description>This page is in draft</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changelog</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/GrandDocs/manual/changelog/</guid>
      <description> Content (including procedures and forms) may change without notice. Check with the Owners Corporation manager for updates.  Revision Control             Revision Date Change Prepared by    1.0.0 2020-02-18 Initial release. Peter Parsons (OC)    2.0.0 2020-04-03 Updated access token order forms Peter Parsons (OC)     </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>