<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Keith Dunstan</title>
    <link>https://keithdunstan.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Keith Dunstan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://keithdunstan.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Doing this is like sitting naked in the bath while a television crew films you for the &amp;lsquo;Today&amp;rsquo; show. A dreadful experience. So why do it? Vanity? It is an act of vanity, yes. But I must put in a plea of guilty with extenuating circumstances.
Heaven knows how many times I have thought about my great-grandfather John Dunstan, a tin miner who was born in Penryn, Cornwall, in 1833.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A nice suburb</title>
      <link>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/a_nice_suburb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/a_nice_suburb/</guid>
      <description>It is much easier to write a novel or an autobiography if you have been miserable as a child, persecuted, tortured or banished. That is why the Russians Dostoevsky, Tolstoy, Turgenev and Gogol remain the greatest writers. Not only were they able to draw on their own emotional, anguished lives; they were also able to call upon the sufferings of their country: upon the poverty, the class conflicts, the frigid winters, the wars and the subjugation of the Russian people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education by flagellation</title>
      <link>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/education_by_flagelation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/education_by_flagelation/</guid>
      <description>So many people look upon school-days as the happiest time of their life. For me school was little pleasure. I suspect my misery was self-inflicted. Home was such a warm, pleasurable place; school such a hideous, disciplined contrast. At the age of 7 1 was dispatched to Wadhurst, the preparatory school for Melbourne Grammar, which was in the grounds of the senior school. Melbourne Grammar, Anglican, bluestone, was created by Bishop Perry in 1849 and was one of the great public schools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siberia</title>
      <link>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/siberia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/siberia/</guid>
      <description>The Geelong Road in 1939 was the epitome of dreariness. One proceeded out past Flemington race-track, through Footscray, through industrial Deer Park, then on to a treeless, rocky plain. The plain seemed waterless, burnt, grey. The only feature, over there to the right, was those humps, rather mysterious, all alone - the You Yangs. The road passed through Werribee, a small town, but I always had a feeling of passing through a wasteland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Following a VC</title>
      <link>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/following_a_vc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/following_a_vc/</guid>
      <description>The Second World War brought with it a sense of obligation and duty that hung heavily, indeed. The Second World War was to us precisely like the First World War, a war between good and evil. Good was Great Britain, King George, the Queen and the unquestioned loyalty of the British Empire. Evil was the Kaiser, the terrible wickedness of Germans and, with the advent of the Second World War, Hitler and the Nazis and their aim to dominate the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stevedore</title>
      <link>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/the_stevedore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/the_stevedore/</guid>
      <description>The Melbounie Cricket Ground was cold and cheerless. I was becoming used to it now. Every posting had meant a few days - and sometimes weeks or months - at the MCG, waiting, waiting for something to happen. The armed forces were always a very good lesson in patience. You learned very early not to question, that you were an object waiting to be moved.The Melbourne Cricket Ground was now a very curious place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Byline Dreamer</title>
      <link>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/byline_dreamer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/byline_dreamer/</guid>
      <description>At last it was back to Australia and 1 PD at the Melbourne Cricket Ground. Within days I was discharged. The farewell gesture from the RAAF was an appalling Victory suit, one of those austerity suits invented by Mr Dedman, Minister for Post War Reconstruction. It was cuffless, narrow of lapel and free of lining and had no shape whatever. My father thought differently. He had a cousin, J. Dunstan Lewis, who had a business in the T &amp;amp; G Building, Collins Street.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Correspondent</title>
      <link>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/correspondent/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/correspondent/</guid>
      <description>Of course, as a honeymoon, it was beyond most people&amp;rsquo;s dreams: a flight across the Pacific in a Boeing Stratocruiser. This was a large, four-engine, propeller-driven aircraft. Journalists by order of the Australian Journalists&amp;rsquo; Association had to travel first class. The Stratocruisers actually had beds - very narrow ones, but beds nevertheless, with curtains like railway Pullmans. So we slept together at an altitude of 4500 to 6000 metres, across the Pacific.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walking the tightrope</title>
      <link>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/walking_the_tightrope/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/walking_the_tightrope/</guid>
      <description>On 5 October 1952 Sir Keith Murdoch died in his sleep at Cruden Farm, Victoria, aged 66 years. He had been into hospital for his second prostate operation the previous April, and his heart gave out. My father thought this event so climactic that he telephoned me in Wallington to give me the news immediately. International telephone calls were not overcommon in 1952. I had sent Dad a photograph of myself near the telephone in our Wallington house and he had craftily read the number on the handset, using a magnifying glass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apits</title>
      <link>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/apits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/apits/</guid>
      <description>We returned to Melbourne with mixed feelings, although by now we were used to being uprooted and moved. It is the same whenever you leave any city, any house where you have been happy. In every move you die just a little. Melbourne in the 1950s and 1980s was a curious, inhibited city, suffering from an inferiority complex. It had never quite overcome the shock, the trauma of those terrible days in 1893 when the banks closed their doors and so-called Marvellous Melbourne went into depression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Antis</title>
      <link>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/the_antis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/the_antis/</guid>
      <description>The great difficulty with the Anti Football League was getting people to believe that we were serious. The wife of a United States ambassador, Mrs Ed Clark, had the best line about Australia. She had the feeling she was living in a gymnasium, she said. Australians rarely seem to be beyond the sound of a bouncing ball. Almost since the first white settlement we have been obsessed with sport. As the nineteenth-century immigrants moved inland the first items they built in any town were the pub, the racetrack, the school and the church, often in that order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jumping the genration gap</title>
      <link>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/jumping_the_generation_gap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/jumping_the_generation_gap/</guid>
      <description>Jumping the generation gapWriters are merciless. Everything that takes place, everything that impinges, is another raisin in the editorial pudding. During casual conversation or at dinner parties the haunted writer is hunting for material, checking over the conversation wondering what can be used. Columnists are the worst; their eyes and ears are on the alert, every waking hour. They are the worst because their need is the greatest. The column is a vast vacuum that sucks in all that is available and the vacuum is there daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pedalling passion</title>
      <link>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/pedalling_passion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/pedalling_passion/</guid>
      <description>You have heard of born-again Christians. Born-again cyclists are similar. My conversion came on an autumn afternoon in 1984. Melbourne had a massive transport strike: no trains, no trams, no buses. Our house at Central Park Road, East Malvern, was 12 kilometres from Flinders Street. Just to write a funny newspaper column about alternative forms of transport I borrowed a bicycle from Malvern Star and rode to town.
It was not funny at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The virus</title>
      <link>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/the_virus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/the_virus/</guid>
      <description>Most journalists have a dream of writing something else, a film script, a play, a book, an item beyond daily news. Everything they write is ephemeral: news today, gone the next. So often as a columnist I received the message, &amp;lsquo;Yes, I read your column, usually in the smallest room in the house&amp;rsquo;. The symbolism of that message did not go unnoticed.
Then there was the other message, the dire warning made by Dad, &amp;lsquo;There is no money in journalism&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Index of contents</title>
      <link>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/index_of_contents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithdunstan.org/books/no_brains_at_all/index_of_contents/</guid>
      <description>St Catherine&amp;rsquo;s school 12 Ste Anne&amp;rsquo;s 6-8, 11, 28, 40, 80,164,186 Saturday matinees 35 Scherger, Air Commodore F. R. W. 83, 103, 104, 106 Schofield, Margaret 133 school athletics 53-4 school cadets 82-3 Schultze, Albert 237, 240 Schultze, Wilma 237 Scotch College 23, 24 Scotts Hotel 170 Scrooge Society 206 sea travel 141-2 Second World War 64, 65-6, 70, 71-2,74-8 see also Royal Australian Air Force Sharpley, Cecil Herbert 187-9 Sherman, Stan 151 shipping round 114 Siple, Greg 230 Sister C.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://keithdunstan.org/about_keith/eulogy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithdunstan.org/about_keith/eulogy/</guid>
      <description>Keith Dunstan (3 February 1925 – 11 September 2013)
Keith Dunstan’s life is not quite an open book. But there is plenty of material there. Not only in his 1990 autobiography No Brains at All, but in countless newspaper columns and features. As a writer Keith Dunstan drew on his own experience. Always with humour and a touch of self-deprecation.
He had the knack of getting his readers to feel they were his friend, as his friend Barry Humphries observed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://keithdunstan.org/books/batman_in_the_bulletin/index_of_contents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithdunstan.org/books/batman_in_the_bulletin/index_of_contents/</guid>
      <description>This section is in draft</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://keithdunstan.org/books/melbourne_i_remember/bookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithdunstan.org/books/melbourne_i_remember/bookies/</guid>
      <description>tags: bookies, Douglas Fairbanks,Dr Coppel Q.C, Mr Justice Taylor, Sir Chester Manifold, TAB
THE FORTRESS AFFAIR – OR SP IN THE RAW The Bulletin 15 September 1962
Australia has always had an affection for Royal Commissions, inquiries, and such. One researcher has pointed out that since 1850 we have had 700 Royal Commissions, both State and Federal. Our colleagues and late colleagues have not shown nearly the same interest. Canada has had a mere 200, New Zealand 160 and South Africa 150.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://keithdunstan.org/books/melbourne_i_remember/corio_capers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keithdunstan.org/books/melbourne_i_remember/corio_capers/</guid>
      <description>tags: Geelong Grammar School, Dr Francis Brown, James Ralph Darling,
Corio Capers One mellows with the years and now I look more kindly upon my years at Geelong Grammar and its famous headmaster of those years, James Darling, in particular. It was the Bulletin editor, Peter Hastings, who urged me to write about my school years and it must have been several years after the story appeared that I met James Darling in Collins Street.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>