<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Keith Dunstan</title>
    <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Keith Dunstan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1. Definitions and Interpretation</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/1definitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/1definitions/</guid>
      <description>1.1	Definitions In these Rules:
Access Token means a device that provides access to or within the Building, including the car park, and that contains security credentials, access privileges, and identifies the user.
Building means a building as defined in the Owners Corporations Act 2006 (VIC) excluding the car park and swimming pool.
Executive Director means the Executive Director of Heritage Victoria.
GST means a goods and services tax, consumption tax, value added tax, retail turnover tax or a tax of a similar nature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1. Introduction</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/introduction/</guid>
      <description>1.1.	Purpose and scope The purpose of this Owners and Residents Manual is to provide information to assist Lot Owners and tenants to live harmoniously and safely at Grand Central Apartments.
The scope of the Manual includes useful contact information for tradespeople who have knowledge and experience at Grand Central Apartments, moving in, around and out of the building, security, recreational facilities, procedures adopted by the Owners Corporation relevant to Lot Owners (such as renovation procedures), and the Owners Corporation Rules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. Principal service providers</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/principal-service-providers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/principal-service-providers/</guid>
      <description>2.1.	Owners Corporation manager Civium Property Group ensures that administrative, financial and regulatory requirements are managed in a timely and effective manner. These include:
 Communication with Lot Owners and Agents, such as the distribution of agenda and meeting minutes, administering ballots, and general correspondence. Invoicing levy amounts, collecting any overdue fees and account enquiries. Paying bills on behalf of the Owners Corporation. Maintaining bank and other financial accounts. Regulatory requirements, such as appropriate insurance coverage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. Rules and Laws</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/2rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/2rules/</guid>
      <description>2.1	Rules (a)	These Rules exist for the purpose of controlling, managing and administering the use and enjoyment of Common Property and Lots. (b)	These Rules are binding on: (i)	Lot Owners; (ii)	Occupiers; (iii)	the Owners Corporation; and (iv)	lessees, licensees and/or sub-lessees or sub-licensees of Common Property.
2.2	Compliance with Rules and Laws (a)	Lot Owners and Occupiers must, and Lot Owners must ensure that Occupiers, at their own cost and in a timely manner, comply with all Rules and Laws relating to:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3. Contact list</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/contact-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/contact-list/</guid>
      <description>Table 2 lists useful contacts for Lot Owners and residents. Some matters are the responsibility of individual Lot Owners (such as internet access), however some companies are listed that have experience in Grand Central Apartments. To that extent, they may provide knowledgeable service. The Owners Corporation does not endorse and is not responsible for the performance of service providers engaged by Lot Owners.
Table 2 – Service providers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3. Owner&#39;s Obligations</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/3ownersobligations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/3ownersobligations/</guid>
      <description>3.1	Use of Lot (a)	Lot Owners must, and must ensure that the Occupier of the Lot complies with any directions made or action taken by the Owners Corporation pursuant to the duty of the Owners Corporation to manage and administer Common Property under the Act.
(b)	A Lot Owner must not and must ensure that the Occupier does not and the Occupier must not:
(i)	use Common Property or permit Common Property to be used in such a manner as to unreasonably interfere with or prevent its use by other Lot Owners or Occupiers or their invitees unless agreed in writing by the Owners Corporation;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4. Alterations to Lots and Common Property</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/4alterations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/4alterations/</guid>
      <description>4.1	Alterations to services to Lots Lot Owners and Occupiers may not without the prior written consent of the Owners Corporation alter gas, water, drainage, septic, sewerage, electrical or any other utility connections and services to a Lot.
4.2	Alterations to Common Property Lot Owners and Occupiers must not:
(a)	alter;
(b)	paint or otherwise mark;
(c)	core into concrete slabs;
(d)	drive nails or anything else into; or
(e)	otherwise damage or deface,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4. Moving in and out</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/moving-in-and-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/moving-in-and-out/</guid>
      <description>Where moving in and out of the Grand Central includes moving furniture and other bulky items, the move must be coordinated with the Building Manager. A loading bay is available near the southern entrance to the rear car park, where moving vans and trucks may be unloaded and loaded.
When moving in for the first time, the Building Manager will provide new residents with induction training, including where to place rubbish, how to access the building and common areas (such as the barbecues and swimming pool), and where to get mail, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5. Building access</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/building-access/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/building-access/</guid>
      <description>5.1.	Security A security system is installed to prevent unauthorised access to the building, rear courtyard and car park. The effective operation of security elements of the building is the collective responsibility of all residents and visitors (including tradespeople).
Electronic locks restrict access to the following areas.
 In and out of the building (and to Levels 1, 2 and 3). To the rear courtyard and barbecues. To the swimming pool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5. Vehicles and parking</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/5vehicles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/5vehicles/</guid>
      <description>(a)	Lot Owners and Occupiers must not, and must ensure that its guest(s) or invitee(s) do not, unless in the case of an emergency:
(i)	park or leave a vehicle, or permit a vehicle, to be parked or left:
(A)	on Common Property, except in designated car spaces; or
(B)	in car park Lots owned by other Lot Owners;
(ii)	fail to comply with any directions of the Owners Corporation, including through the Building Manager, in relation to car parking;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6. Apartment services</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/apartment-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/apartment-services/</guid>
      <description>6.1.	Concierge Grand Central Apartments does not have a concierge service. The principal service providers only work during normal business hours. Residents should not use the Hotel as a proxy for a concierge. Whilst the Hotel and residents live and work together, the Hotel is a business and should not be treated as an after-hours service provider to greet resident’s guests, receive packages or food deliveries, or solve apartment after-hours service problems (such as electricity failure or dripping taps).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7. Security</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/6insurance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/6insurance/</guid>
      <description>6.1	Restrictions A person must not bring to, do or keep anything on a Lot which:
(a)	will increase the rate of premium for insurance on another Lot or Common Property;
(b)	conflicts with Laws relating to fire or any insurance policy on another Lot or Common Property.
6.2	Insurance All Lot Owners must ensure that any improvements within a Lot are in compliance with all laws and legal requirements and in keeping with Good Manufacturing Practice standards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7. Security</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/7security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/7security/</guid>
      <description>7.1	Common Property Security (a)	The Owners Corporation may arrange and operate a security system to monitor the Land affected by the Owners Corporation.
(b)	The Owners Corporation
(i)	is responsible for control of the security system; and
(ii)	may employ servants, agents or contractors to operate any security system.
7.2	Security Arrangements (a)	At the discretion of the Owners Corporation, the security arrangements may include, without limitation:
(i)	security of Common Property against entry by unauthorised person(s);</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7. Waste</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/waste/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/waste/</guid>
      <description>7.1.	General and recycling Except for Level 1, there are two rubbish rooms, located at the northern and southern end of each level. The rubbish rooms include separate bins for recycling. Residents should sort domestic rubbish, mixed recycling waste and cardboard waste, and place it in the appropriate bins.
7.2.	Hard waste Hard waste (large items, such as appliances) is generally collected every three months. The Building Manager will notify residents when a collection is imminent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8. Maintenance</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/maintenance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/maintenance/</guid>
      <description>8.1.	Plumbing and drainage Plumbing and drainage within an apartment is the responsibility of the Lot Owner. This includes leaking taps, burst hot water services and blocked drains.
Where water is entering an apartment from an adjacent apartment, then the Owners Corporation may investigate the cause of the leak and have the leak stopped to prevent damage. Such leaks will be investigated to determine the cause. Where a leak is caused by a failure of common property, then the Owners Corporation will pay for the costs of rectification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8. Waste Collection</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/8waste/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/8waste/</guid>
      <description>Each Lot Owner and Occupier must:
(a)	be aware of and adhere to the Waste Management Agreement;
(b)	at all times protect waste deposited in designated areas against the attraction of flies or other vermin by wrapping the waste in paper or other suitable material;
(c)	not place or caused to be placed in the receptacle any refuse, or other thing which is aflame, smouldering, sludge, alive or not waste;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9. Notice of Accidents or Damage to Property</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/9notice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/9notice/</guid>
      <description>A Lot Owner and Occupier must notify the Owners Corporation promptly of:
(a)	any accident or death that may arise on Common Property;
(b)	any accident to or defect in any water pipes, gas pipes, electric installations, drainage pipes, fixtures or any other utility infrastructure; or
(c)	any damage to or breakage of Common Property which comes to the Lot Owners&amp;rsquo; or Occupiers&amp;rsquo; knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9. Parking </title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/parking/</guid>
      <description>9.1.	General Parking is only available in designated car park lots in the car park building at the rear of the main building. Limited parking is available in the loading bay while loading and unloading furniture and other bulky items. The common area at the south of the building (around the fountain) is not a recognised car park.
9.2.	Car park building Vehicles can only be parked in designated park lots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10. Contractors</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/10contractors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/10contractors/</guid>
      <description>10.1	No Instruction Lot Owners and Occupiers must not directly instruct any contractors or workers employed by the Owners Corporation unless specifically authorised to do so.
10.2	Owners Corporation Representative All requests for the Owners Corporation to consider giving directions on a particular matter to a contractor or worker must be directed to the Manager of the Owners Corporation, who will in turn refer the request to the Owners Corporation for determination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10. Recreation</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/recreation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/recreation/</guid>
      <description>10.1.	Swimming pool The swimming pool on Level 1 is open each day from 0600 to 2200. General safety and social responsibility rules apply in and around the swimming pool.
10.2.	Spa The spa is adjacent to the swimming pool. The spa is open each day from 0600 to 2200. Foreign products (such as soap) should not be added to the spa.
10.3.	Sauna The sauna is owned by the Hotel and with its consent, may be used by all residents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11. Notification of Infectious Diseases</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/11notification/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/11notification/</guid>
      <description>11.1	Notice Lot Owners and Occupiers must, if any infectious disease, which may require notification by virtue of any statute, regulation or ordinance, affects any person in any Lot give, or cause to be given, notice of that fact and any other information which may be required relative to the disease to the Owners Corporation.
11.2	Expenses The Lot Owner and Occupiers must pay to the Owners Corporation the expenses of disinfecting or isolating the affected Lot (if that is necessary) and replacing any article or thing the destruction of which may be rendered necessary by such disease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11. Renovations</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/renovations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/renovations/</guid>
      <description>Renovations within an apartment may be lengthy and disruptive to other residents. Lot Owners need to be aware that Heritage Victoria restrictions apply to the whole of the building and surrounding land. Changes may affect heritage aspects of the building and need to be approved. Annex 5 provides details of a procedure adopted to regulate renovations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12. Owners Corporation Rules and Notices</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/12ownerscorporationrules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/12ownerscorporationrules/</guid>
      <description>12.1	Notices to be Observed Each Lot Owner and Occupier must observe the terms of any notice displayed on any part of Common Property by authority of the Owners Corporation or of any statutory authority.
12.2	Invitees (a)	Each Lot Owner and Occupier must:
(i)	ensure any invitees comply with these Rules; and
(ii)	if an invitee fails to comply, forthwith cause that invitee to leave the land affected by the Owners Corporation as soon as reasonably practicable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12. Special Rules</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/special-rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/special-rules/</guid>
      <description>The Special Rules in Annex 6 are adopted by the Owners Corporation to control, manage and administer the use and enjoyment of common property.
Lot Owners and residents (including tenants) should be familiar with the Special Rules. The Special Rules include both positive and negative obligations on all Owners, residents and their guests. A breach of the Special Rules may result in action taken by the Owners Corporation to remedy the breach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>13.	Retail / Commercial Lots</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/13retail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/13retail/</guid>
      <description>13.1	Planning Permit and Licences Retail / Commercial Lot applying for, and obtaining, any planning permit, liquor licence, or any retail or commercial legislative consent or permit which the Lot Owner or Occupier of any Retail / Commercial Lot may require, provided at all times the Lot Owner or Occupier of any such Retail / Commercial Lot:
(a)	operates lawfully;
(b)	obtains each and every permit, liquor licence or other consent required;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annex 1 – Move in, Move out, Induction</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/annex-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/annex-1/</guid>
      <description>This page is in draft</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>14. Provision and Support of Services</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/14provision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/14provision/</guid>
      <description>14.1	Provision of Services Lot Owners must not interfere with or modify any Building service, including but not limited to air conditioning, heating or ventilation systems or associated ducts or pipes, servicing Lot Owners&amp;rsquo; Lots, all Land affected by the Owners Corporation, the Building or Common Property without the prior written consent of the Owners Corporation.
14.2	Support of Services Lot Owners must not do anything or permit anything to be done to Lot Owners&amp;rsquo; Lots or Common Property, without the written consent of the Owners Corporation, so that:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annex 2 – Access Tokens and Apartment Door Keys</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/annex-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/annex-2/</guid>
      <description>This page is in draft</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annex 3 – Use of Car Park by Non-Residents</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/annex-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/annex-3/</guid>
      <description>This page is in draft</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15.	Storage of Bicycles and Personal Items</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/15storage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/15storage/</guid>
      <description>(a)	A Lot Owner or Occupier cannot hold the Owners Corporation responsible in the event that their bicycle is stolen or damaged whilst stored on Common Property of the Building.
(b)	Lot Owners and Occupiers must not permit any personal items to be stored for any length of time on Common Property without the prior written consent of the Owners Corporation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annex 4 – Car Park Storage Pods and Bollards</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/annex-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/annex-4/</guid>
      <description>This page is in draft</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>16. Fire and Smoke Control</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/16fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/16fire/</guid>
      <description>(a)	Lot Owners and Occupiers must not:
(i)	keep inflammable material on Owners&amp;rsquo; Lot or any part of Common Property except as permitted by these Rules;
(ii)	interfere with fire safety equipment; or
(iii)	obstruct fire stairs or fire escapes.
(b)	Lot Owners and Occupiers must ensure that:
(i)	Lot Owners and Occupiers comply with all Laws about fire safety;
(ii)	all fire safety equipment in Owners&amp;rsquo; Lot or on parts of Common Property is at all times operational; and</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annex 5 – Renovations</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/annex-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/annex-5/</guid>
      <description>This page is in draft</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>17. Owners Corporation Manager</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/17ownerscorporationmanager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/17ownerscorporationmanager/</guid>
      <description>17.1	Owners Corporation Manager (a)	If the Owners Corporation has appointed an Owners Corporation Manager and given notice of that appointment to a Lot Owner, the Lot Owner is entitled to and must assume that the Owners Corporation Manager is entitled to take any action on behalf of the Owners Corporation under these Rules.
(b)	A person must not interfere with or stop the Owners Corporation Manager from:
(i)	performing its obligations or exercising its rights under its agreement with the Owners Corporation; or</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annex 6 – Special Rules</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/annex-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/annex-6/</guid>
      <description>This page is in draft</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>18. Notices and Compliance</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/18notices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/18notices/</guid>
      <description>18.1	Address of New Owners (a)	A Lot Owner who sells a Lot must advise the Owners Corporation of the name and address of the new owner within one month of the completion of the contract.
(b)	A person who acquires a Lot must advise the Owners Corporation of the person&amp;rsquo;s name, email (where available), contact telephone number and address within one month of the completion of the sale and purchase contract.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>19. Complaints and Dispute Resolution</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/19complaints/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/19complaints/</guid>
      <description>19.1	Complaints (a)	Lot Owners, Occupiers and/or the Owners Corporation Manager may make a complaint with regard to any breach of these Rules or any applicable Laws and regulations by:
(i)	a Lot Owner;
(ii)	an Occupier; or
(iii)	Owners Corporation Manager.
(b)	All complaints must be:
(i)	in writing; and
(ii)	in the approved form as required by Laws from time to time.
(c)	All complaints must be brought to the attention of:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20. GST payment</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/20gst/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/20gst/</guid>
      <description>If the Owners Corporation is liable by law for any GST on any Primary Payment, the Lot Owner must pay to the Owners Corporation the amount of the GST in addition to the Primary Payment at the same time and in the same manner as the Lot Owner is required to pay the Primary Payment in respect of which the GST relates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>21.	Heritage Victoria Requirements</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/22heritage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/22heritage/</guid>
      <description>(a)	The Owners Corporation shall take all action necessary or desirable to preserve, maintain and care for the Registered Place to the satisfaction of the Heritage Council.
(b)	The Owners Corporation and the owners of all lots acknowledge that the Registered Place is of cultural heritage significance and is No. 699 on the Victorian Heritage Register.
(c)	The Owners Corporation shall be entitled to levy and recover from Lot Owners special fees or charges to establish a fund to cover the maintenance and restoration of the Registered Place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>22. Hotel Lots</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/22hotel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/22hotel/</guid>
      <description>(a)	The Hotel for the time being shall have unrestricted access to Common Property (including any exclusive use areas and special privilege areas referred to in these rules) for the purpose of the Hotel properly and effectively exercising its rights and obligations under the Liquor Act (or any other relevant statute) for the purpose of carrying on the business of a licensed restaurant, bar, liquor shop, hotel and providing a mini bar and room service to Lot Owners or Occupiers of other Lots in the Building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>23. Relocations, Deliveries, Tradespeople and Moving of Articles</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/23relocations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/23relocations/</guid>
      <description>A Lot Owner must not, and must ensure that the Occupier of a Lot does not:
(a)	give less than forty-eight (48) hours&amp;rsquo; notice to the Owners Corporation or its representative before any furniture, fittings, furnishings or equipment may be moved in or out of any Lot and the moving of same must be done in a manner and at the time directed by the representative of the Owners Corporation;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changelog</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/24changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/rules/24changelog/</guid>
      <description>This is version 1.0.0 May 2020</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changelog</title>
      <link>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://batmanian.github.io/KeithDunstan/manual/changelog/</guid>
      <description> Content (including procedures and forms) may change without notice. Check with the Owners Corporation manager for updates.  Revision Control             Revision Date Change Prepared by    1.0.0 2020-02-18 Initial release. Peter Parsons (OC)    2.0.0 2020-04-03 Updated access token order forms Peter Parsons (OC)     </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>